Tired?
Go to sleep.
I'm really tired.
Stop it.
Honey,
I see you're sleeping deeply,
so I didn't wake you up.
I'm going to Fan State for a business trip,
and I'll be back in a few days.
Some men feel guilty
feel
guilty.
To cover up their cheating,
they become overly affectionate with their wives.
Ah.
Honey.
Why are you in France?
[The scent of an expensive perfume.]
[This smell seems familiar.]
What a beautiful bracelet.
Clive Christian.
Number one.
We're taking off.
I'm dizzy.
Go to school first.
I'll play with you
when you get back.
Okay.
Go.
Give it to me.
What a surprise.
I didn't expect you to be so patient with children.
Are you like this with all children?
Or even the children of your enemies
can be used as pawns?
Do your own job well.
I don't have that much patience.
No, Jiang Li, this is too tight.
Make it a bit looser.
If it's any looser,
the dress won't hold its shape.
Is this really made to my measurements?
Maybe we should let it out another two centimeters.
Qianqian.
What's wrong?
You look so worried.
Is something on your mind?
Jiang Li,
do you recognize this bracelet?
It was designed by a young designer,
but she passed away.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Your waist-to-hip ratio
is really enviable.
If I were a man,
I would definitely take you down.
Perfect makeup.
Tender hands.
The halo of the eldest daughter of the Lu family.
Be more confident.
Whether it was six years ago or now,
no matter who it was,
they would choose you,
not me.
We are best friends.
Of course, we are.
Relax.
Your wedding is in two days.
This is your first wedding,
and your last.
I'm leaving now.
Jiang Li, wait a moment.
Do you like this car?
This is...
A gift for you.
Go ahead,
what do you need me to do?
I just thought
you would need a car when you come back.
So...
You're not like this.
[Your brother-in-law might be cheating.]
[If it's true,]
[find this woman.]
[Why me?]
[Because you're a wild grass trying to climb out of the mud,]
[and I]
[can give you everything you want.]
[Isn't that right?]
[Including shares of Golden Thread.]
Cheers!
Pour the wine.
Come on.
Cheers.
Xiaorou,
this Chanel suit is tailor-made for you.
Of course.
Xiaorou is a career woman.
Look at this bracelet.
It's a full diamond model from Bvlgari.
You've never seen it, right?
It's over 300,000 yuan.
Bvlgari?
So beautiful!
This bracelet is the cheapest
on her.
And these earrings
from Graff,
worth eight figures.
Wow!
My goodness!
I'm so jealous!
It's stunning!
What business does Xiaorou do?
Take us with you.
Just a small business.
Today's drinks are on us.
Have a good time.
Come on.
To Xiaorou.
Cheers.
Come on, Xiaorou.
Let's go to the next place.
Ah.
You guys go ahead.
I left my lipstick in the private room.
I'll be there in a minute.
We'll go ahead.
Come quickly.
Okay.
We'll go ahead.
We'll order the wine first.
Bye.
Hurry up.
Ah?
Where did it go?
Did you see
an earring?
Earring?
No.
You go out first.
I'll finish cleaning soon.
Go out.
Li Sisi,
are you looking for this?
What are you doing here?
Have some water to sober up.
Chanel suit,
Graff's colored diamond earrings.
Your friends really have no taste.
This pair of pearls is worth millions.
Everything you're wearing,
except for your underwear
and Bvlgari bracelet,
must be Lu Qianqian's.
How do you know?
The car in front of the old house,
that's yours.
You're really the midnight Cinderella.
Li Sisi,
how do you know my old name?
You've looked into my background.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I haven't decided yet.
But I can pretend
I don't know about today.
You're so kind?
Of course not.
I have a condition.
You've been living in the Lu family
and Golden Thread for six years.
If you don't want Lu Qianqian to know,
you have to be obedient
and provide me with useful information.
By the way,
where did Zhou Jian go?
Who did he meet?
I know he didn't go to Fan State,
but changed his route halfway.
If you don't tell me,
I'll let Lu Qianqian ask you in person.
Mr. Zhou went to Bin Hai.
I heard that Mr. Zhuang would go to Bin Hai
for a vacation in the next few days.
I'll get in touch with you later.
Mr. Zhou is really well-informed.
You even know that I'm on vacation
in Bin Hai.
Mr. Zhuang, you are too kind.
I happened to be on a business trip in Er City,
and I heard from a friend that
you were on vacation nearby.
So,
I thought I'd come and see if I could meet you.
Annie,
you may not know,
but the chairman just had surgery,
and I haven't been bothering her much lately.
I'm actually quite embarrassed,
I was thinking of inviting you,
but you're the one who invited me.
I didn't expect you to invite me.
It doesn't matter.
I've invited some friends anyway.
They are not strangers.
Then let's just eat together.
I didn't expect to see
Mr. Shen here.
Nice to meet you.
I came to see my cousin-in-law
to discuss some family matters.
So I just came over uninvited
to join the fun.
After all,
this isn't the first time Mr. Zhou and I have met.
Have we met before?
In the elevator.
Do you remember?
Ah.
Maybe Mr. Zhou was in a hurry at that time,
so you didn't notice me.
By the way,
when will your friend arrive?
Isn't it Mr Shen
that Mr Zhuang mentioned?
Jingmo is my family.
How could she be my friend?
She said she would come
after changing clothes.
She should
be arriving soon.